let questions = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question:
        "  In a quadrilateral, if one angle is 120° and the other three angles are congruent, what type of quadrilateral is it?",
      answer: "A. Parallelogram",
      options: ["A. Parallelogram", "B. Rhombus", "C. Trapezoid", "D. Kite"],
    },
  
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: " Given a polygon with interior angles measuring 120°, 150°, 100°, and 90°, determine the type of polygon.",
      answer: "B. Quadrilateral",
      options: [
        "A. Triangle",
        "B. Quadrilateral",
        "C. Pentagon",
        "D. Hexagon",
      ],
    },
  
    {
      numb: 3,
      question:
        "If the exterior angle of a regular polygon is 45°, what is the interior angle of the polygon?",
      answer: "B. 135°",
      options: [
        "A. 120°",
        "B. 135°",
        "C. 150°",
        "D. 165°",
      ],
    },
  
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "In a triangle with angles measuring 30°, 60°, and 90°, classify the triangle based on angles.",
      answer: "B. Right-angled",
      options: ["A. Acute-angled", "B. Right-angled", "C. Obtuse-angled", "D. Equilateral"],
    },
  
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: " If the sum of interior angles in a polygon is 1080° and it is a convex polygon, how many sides does the polygon have?",
      answer: "C. 8",
      options: [
        "A. 6",
        "B. 7",
        "C. 8",
        "D. 9",
      ],
    },

    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "Given a triangle with side lengths of 5 cm, 6 cm, and 7 cm, determine the type of triangle.",
      answer: "A. Scalene",
      options: [
        "A. Scalene",
        "B. Isosceles",
        "C. Equilateral",
        "D. Right-angled",
      ],
    },

    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "If the interior angles of a polygon form an arithmetic sequence and the smallest angle is 120°, what is the measure of the largest angle?",
      answer: "C. 200°",
      options: [
        "A. 160°",
        "B. 180°",
        "C. 200°",
        "D. 220°",
      ],
    },

    {
      numb: 8,
      question: " In a regular polygon, if the measure of each interior angle is 150°, what is the sum of interior angles in the polygon?",
      answer: "D. 1080°",
      options: [
        "A. 540°",
        "B. 720°",
        "C. 900°",
        "D. 1080°",
      ],
    },

    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "  Given a quadrilateral with angles of 80°, 100°, 120°, and 160°, determine if the quadrilateral is a parallelogram.",
      answer: "A. Yes",
      options: [
        "A. Yes",
        "B. No",
        "C. Cannot be determined",
        "D. Not applicable",
      ],
    },

    {
      numb: 10,
      question: " If a regular polygon has 10 sides, what is the measure of each exterior angle?",
      answer: "B. 36°",
      options: [
        "A. 30°",
        "B. 36°",
        "C. 45°",
        "D. 60°",
      ],
    },
  ];
  